{
    "addition": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "451 + 830",
                "answer": 1281
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "457 + 947",
                "answer": 1404
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "588 + 599",
                "answer": 1187
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "15 + 108",
                "answer": 123
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "603 + 356",
                "answer": 959
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "22 + 228",
                "answer": 250
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "864 + 275",
                "answer": 1139
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "420 + 760",
                "answer": 1180
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "265 + 958",
                "answer": 1223
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "193 + 507",
                "answer": 700
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "978 + 529",
                "answer": 1507
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "631 + 894",
                "answer": 1525
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "974 + 731",
                "answer": 1705
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "879 + 796",
                "answer": 1675
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "419 + 612",
                "answer": 1031
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "620 + 974",
                "answer": 1594
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "636 + 877",
                "answer": 1513
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "909 + 714",
                "answer": 1623
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "594 + 524",
                "answer": 1118
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "190 + 684",
                "answer": 874
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "289 + 936",
                "answer": 1225
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "36 + 687",
                "answer": 723
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "75 + 405",
                "answer": 480
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "21 + 18",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "699 + 730",
                "answer": 1429
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "908 + 595",
                "answer": 1503
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "389 + 810",
                "answer": 1199
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "730 + 979",
                "answer": 1709
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "926 + 413",
                "answer": 1339
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "166 + 556",
                "answer": 722
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "215 + 420",
                "answer": 635
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "51 + 130",
                "answer": 181
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "736 + 441",
                "answer": 1177
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "392 + 514",
                "answer": 906
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "641 + 626",
                "answer": 1267
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "525 + 922",
                "answer": 1447
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "887 + 591",
                "answer": 1478
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "126 + 817",
                "answer": 943
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "793 + 65",
                "answer": 858
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "622 + 502",
                "answer": 1124
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "536 + 862",
                "answer": 1398
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "292 + 934",
                "answer": 1226
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "251 + 267",
                "answer": 518
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "578 + 711",
                "answer": 1289
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "505 + 286",
                "answer": 791
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "214 + 840",
                "answer": 1054
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "327 + 391",
                "answer": 718
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "903 + 268",
                "answer": 1171
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "846 + 751",
                "answer": 1597
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "567 + 449",
                "answer": 1016
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "917 + 891",
                "answer": 1808
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "419 + 897",
                "answer": 1316
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "222 + 549",
                "answer": 771
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "592 + 834",
                "answer": 1426
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "356 + 481",
                "answer": 837
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "284 + 594",
                "answer": 878
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "605 + 506",
                "answer": 1111
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "156 + 312",
                "answer": 468
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "292 + 912",
                "answer": 1204
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "892 + 799",
                "answer": 1691
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "139 + 107",
                "answer": 246
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "252 + 231",
                "answer": 483
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "671 + 554",
                "answer": 1225
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "512 + 638",
                "answer": 1150
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "9 + 792",
                "answer": 801
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "534 + 132",
                "answer": 666
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "155 + 541",
                "answer": 696
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "335 + 800",
                "answer": 1135
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "378 + 546",
                "answer": 924
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "677 + 142",
                "answer": 819
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "927 + 190",
                "answer": 1117
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "171 + 233",
                "answer": 404
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "926 + 635",
                "answer": 1561
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "515 + 351",
                "answer": 866
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "909 + 456",
                "answer": 1365
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "824 + 485",
                "answer": 1309
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "611 + 590",
                "answer": 1201
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "937 + 780",
                "answer": 1717
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "394 + 982",
                "answer": 1376
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "203 + 458",
                "answer": 661
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "204 + 479",
                "answer": 683
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "956 + 819",
                "answer": 1775
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "240 + 799",
                "answer": 1039
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "842 + 547",
                "answer": 1389
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "729 + 844",
                "answer": 1573
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "97 + 846",
                "answer": 943
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "158 + 885",
                "answer": 1043
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "389 + 263",
                "answer": 652
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "962 + 452",
                "answer": 1414
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "302 + 652",
                "answer": 954
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "56 + 650",
                "answer": 706
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "496 + 403",
                "answer": 899
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "423 + 126",
                "answer": 549
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "664 + 159",
                "answer": 823
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "963 + 700",
                "answer": 1663
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "832 + 692",
                "answer": 1524
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "546 + 758",
                "answer": 1304
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "466 + 138",
                "answer": 604
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "35 + 543",
                "answer": 578
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "915 + 169",
                "answer": 1084
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "946 + 873",
                "answer": 1819
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "533 + 459",
                "answer": 992
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "235 + 664",
                "answer": 899
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "231 + 154",
                "answer": 385
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "80 + 339",
                "answer": 419
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "325 + 103",
                "answer": 428
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "889 + 11",
                "answer": 900
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "311 + 265",
                "answer": 576
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "21 + 886",
                "answer": 907
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "811 + 66",
                "answer": 877
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "339 + 166",
                "answer": 505
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "757 + 750",
                "answer": 1507
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "319 + 631",
                "answer": 950
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "665 + 472",
                "answer": 1137
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "307 + 563",
                "answer": 870
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "160 + 211",
                "answer": 371
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "690 + 742",
                "answer": 1432
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "352 + 450",
                "answer": 802
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "391 + 612",
                "answer": 1003
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "582 + 50",
                "answer": 632
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "53 + 433",
                "answer": 486
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "765 + 532",
                "answer": 1297
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "843 + 79",
                "answer": 922
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "470 + 453",
                "answer": 923
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "895 + 190",
                "answer": 1085
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "787 + 809",
                "answer": 1596
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "946 + 399",
                "answer": 1345
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "148 + 737",
                "answer": 885
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "634 + 597",
                "answer": 1231
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "209 + 158",
                "answer": 367
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "556 + 760",
                "answer": 1316
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "53 + 544",
                "answer": 597
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "562 + 924",
                "answer": 1486
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "968 + 303",
                "answer": 1271
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "560 + 41",
                "answer": 601
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "515 + 316",
                "answer": 831
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "951 + 761",
                "answer": 1712
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "113 + 109",
                "answer": 222
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "198 + 865",
                "answer": 1063
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "525 + 256",
                "answer": 781
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "717 + 648",
                "answer": 1365
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "122 + 704",
                "answer": 826
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "11 + 139",
                "answer": 150
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "513 + 321",
                "answer": 834
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "779 + 332",
                "answer": 1111
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "714 + 142",
                "answer": 856
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "888 + 842",
                "answer": 1730
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "988 + 797",
                "answer": 1785
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "969 + 868",
                "answer": 1837
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "207 + 864",
                "answer": 1071
            }
        ]
    },
    "subtraction": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "25 - 195",
                "answer": -170
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "513 - 611",
                "answer": -98
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "901 - 102",
                "answer": 799
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "866 - 630",
                "answer": 236
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "171 - 748",
                "answer": -577
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "903 - 717",
                "answer": 186
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "689 - 906",
                "answer": -217
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "692 - 99",
                "answer": 593
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "164 - 105",
                "answer": 59
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "719 - 26",
                "answer": 693
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "790 - 210",
                "answer": 580
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "610 - 867",
                "answer": -257
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "132 - 200",
                "answer": -68
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "369 - 633",
                "answer": -264
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "584 - 839",
                "answer": -255
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "796 - 361",
                "answer": 435
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "8 - 306",
                "answer": -298
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "258 - 327",
                "answer": -69
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "689 - 999",
                "answer": -310
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "66 - 224",
                "answer": -158
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "844 - 651",
                "answer": 193
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "942 - 773",
                "answer": 169
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "692 - 917",
                "answer": -225
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "349 - 952",
                "answer": -603
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "909 - 390",
                "answer": 519
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "208 - 688",
                "answer": -480
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "934 - 550",
                "answer": 384
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "812 - 786",
                "answer": 26
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "621 - 788",
                "answer": -167
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "673 - 879",
                "answer": -206
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "36 - 328",
                "answer": -292
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "682 - 258",
                "answer": 424
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "996 - 160",
                "answer": 836
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "868 - 92",
                "answer": 776
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "635 - 476",
                "answer": 159
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "659 - 129",
                "answer": 530
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "857 - 467",
                "answer": 390
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "585 - 631",
                "answer": -46
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "577 - 462",
                "answer": 115
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "309 - 767",
                "answer": -458
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "61 - 431",
                "answer": -370
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "227 - 180",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "709 - 498",
                "answer": 211
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "743 - 60",
                "answer": 683
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "916 - 30",
                "answer": 886
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "744 - 435",
                "answer": 309
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "163 - 401",
                "answer": -238
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "594 - 51",
                "answer": 543
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "455 - 44",
                "answer": 411
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "738 - 344",
                "answer": 394
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "555 - 199",
                "answer": 356
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "600 - 285",
                "answer": 315
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "715 - 714",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "983 - 959",
                "answer": 24
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "785 - 134",
                "answer": 651
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "5 - 422",
                "answer": -417
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "163 - 953",
                "answer": -790
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "670 - 101",
                "answer": 569
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "372 - 946",
                "answer": -574
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "347 - 679",
                "answer": -332
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "893 - 8",
                "answer": 885
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "750 - 618",
                "answer": 132
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "748 - 283",
                "answer": 465
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "437 - 229",
                "answer": 208
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "141 - 257",
                "answer": -116
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "765 - 966",
                "answer": -201
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "932 - 834",
                "answer": 98
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "84 - 517",
                "answer": -433
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "565 - 365",
                "answer": 200
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "477 - 81",
                "answer": 396
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "813 - 453",
                "answer": 360
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "925 - 453",
                "answer": 472
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "577 - 872",
                "answer": -295
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "860 - 183",
                "answer": 677
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "799 - 702",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "934 - 62",
                "answer": 872
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "67 - 231",
                "answer": -164
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "438 - 559",
                "answer": -121
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "20 - 767",
                "answer": -747
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "332 - 626",
                "answer": -294
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "258 - 219",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "350 - 640",
                "answer": -290
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "254 - 266",
                "answer": -12
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "734 - 629",
                "answer": 105
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "407 - 47",
                "answer": 360
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "10 - 703",
                "answer": -693
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "912 - 960",
                "answer": -48
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "315 - 570",
                "answer": -255
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "352 - 937",
                "answer": -585
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "818 - 614",
                "answer": 204
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "509 - 304",
                "answer": 205
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "400 - 934",
                "answer": -534
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "624 - 13",
                "answer": 611
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "742 - 975",
                "answer": -233
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "308 - 915",
                "answer": -607
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "839 - 109",
                "answer": 730
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "102 - 950",
                "answer": -848
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "520 - 780",
                "answer": -260
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "600 - 208",
                "answer": 392
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "212 - 642",
                "answer": -430
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "878 - 84",
                "answer": 794
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "360 - 399",
                "answer": -39
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "965 - 691",
                "answer": 274
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "591 - 101",
                "answer": 490
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "227 - 329",
                "answer": -102
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "411 - 681",
                "answer": -270
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "66 - 282",
                "answer": -216
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "444 - 638",
                "answer": -194
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "244 - 209",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "527 - 627",
                "answer": -100
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "793 - 738",
                "answer": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "611 - 801",
                "answer": -190
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "652 - 219",
                "answer": 433
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "889 - 781",
                "answer": 108
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "832 - 854",
                "answer": -22
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "778 - 134",
                "answer": 644
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "536 - 6",
                "answer": 530
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "400 - 21",
                "answer": 379
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "309 - 468",
                "answer": -159
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "851 - 831",
                "answer": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "882 - 667",
                "answer": 215
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "627 - 35",
                "answer": 592
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "160 - 428",
                "answer": -268
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "917 - 798",
                "answer": 119
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "630 - 4",
                "answer": 626
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "255 - 560",
                "answer": -305
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "477 - 276",
                "answer": 201
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "786 - 675",
                "answer": 111
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "188 - 60",
                "answer": 128
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "641 - 903",
                "answer": -262
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "872 - 924",
                "answer": -52
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "264 - 87",
                "answer": 177
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "722 - 556",
                "answer": 166
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "374 - 570",
                "answer": -196
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "119 - 124",
                "answer": -5
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "152 - 780",
                "answer": -628
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "937 - 255",
                "answer": 682
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "831 - 88",
                "answer": 743
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "915 - 400",
                "answer": 515
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "313 - 202",
                "answer": 111
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "371 - 572",
                "answer": -201
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "420 - 728",
                "answer": -308
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "296 - 512",
                "answer": -216
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "626 - 10",
                "answer": 616
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "733 - 431",
                "answer": 302
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "766 - 19",
                "answer": 747
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "575 - 764",
                "answer": -189
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "864 - 369",
                "answer": 495
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "16 - 252",
                "answer": -236
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "948 - 387",
                "answer": 561
            }
        ]
    },
    "multiplication": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "45 x 69",
                "answer": 3105
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "40 x 53",
                "answer": 2120
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "52 x 70",
                "answer": 3640
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "58 x 1",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "4 x 38",
                "answer": 152
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "28 x 14",
                "answer": 392
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "84 x 49",
                "answer": 4116
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "43 x 21",
                "answer": 903
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "79 x 80",
                "answer": 6320
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "35 x 51",
                "answer": 1785
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "14 x 70",
                "answer": 980
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "80 x 75",
                "answer": 6000
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "36 x 40",
                "answer": 1440
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "93 x 35",
                "answer": 3255
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "39 x 62",
                "answer": 2418
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "86 x 35",
                "answer": 3010
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "36 x 65",
                "answer": 2340
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "3 x 21",
                "answer": 63
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "35 x 24",
                "answer": 840
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "12 x 78",
                "answer": 936
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "48 x 14",
                "answer": 672
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "7 x 80",
                "answer": 560
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "20 x 37",
                "answer": 740
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "74 x 86",
                "answer": 6364
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "83 x 72",
                "answer": 5976
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "93 x 46",
                "answer": 4278
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "30 x 23",
                "answer": 690
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "97 x 10",
                "answer": 970
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "37 x 81",
                "answer": 2997
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "78 x 86",
                "answer": 6708
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "33 x 9",
                "answer": 297
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "87 x 48",
                "answer": 4176
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "66 x 58",
                "answer": 3828
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "16 x 67",
                "answer": 1072
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "5 x 68",
                "answer": 340
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "81 x 52",
                "answer": 4212
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "99 x 47",
                "answer": 4653
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "92 x 49",
                "answer": 4508
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "58 x 4",
                "answer": 232
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "67 x 63",
                "answer": 4221
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "65 x 6",
                "answer": 390
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "37 x 57",
                "answer": 2109
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "72 x 95",
                "answer": 6840
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "98 x 29",
                "answer": 2842
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "59 x 37",
                "answer": 2183
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "23 x 23",
                "answer": 529
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "40 x 98",
                "answer": 3920
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "37 x 87",
                "answer": 3219
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "100 x 89",
                "answer": 8900
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "68 x 78",
                "answer": 5304
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "7 x 23",
                "answer": 161
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "58 x 33",
                "answer": 1914
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "20 x 51",
                "answer": 1020
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "7 x 44",
                "answer": 308
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "29 x 66",
                "answer": 1914
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "73 x 74",
                "answer": 5402
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "94 x 22",
                "answer": 2068
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "54 x 88",
                "answer": 4752
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "78 x 59",
                "answer": 4602
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "80 x 17",
                "answer": 1360
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "63 x 76",
                "answer": 4788
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "78 x 36",
                "answer": 2808
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "34 x 73",
                "answer": 2482
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "19 x 47",
                "answer": 893
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "36 x 18",
                "answer": 648
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "37 x 1",
                "answer": 37
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "16 x 37",
                "answer": 592
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "88 x 50",
                "answer": 4400
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "27 x 82",
                "answer": 2214
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "96 x 40",
                "answer": 3840
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "11 x 61",
                "answer": 671
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "66 x 98",
                "answer": 6468
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "10 x 100",
                "answer": 1000
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "67 x 66",
                "answer": 4422
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "40 x 10",
                "answer": 400
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "55 x 87",
                "answer": 4785
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "81 x 57",
                "answer": 4617
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "35 x 57",
                "answer": 1995
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "46 x 67",
                "answer": 3082
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "50 x 43",
                "answer": 2150
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "31 x 76",
                "answer": 2356
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "81 x 28",
                "answer": 2268
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "8 x 57",
                "answer": 456
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "24 x 39",
                "answer": 936
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "62 x 47",
                "answer": 2914
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "13 x 71",
                "answer": 923
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "75 x 49",
                "answer": 3675
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "83 x 53",
                "answer": 4399
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "92 x 12",
                "answer": 1104
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "22 x 69",
                "answer": 1518
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "88 x 72",
                "answer": 6336
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "81 x 57",
                "answer": 4617
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "72 x 54",
                "answer": 3888
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "79 x 37",
                "answer": 2923
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "79 x 2",
                "answer": 158
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "22 x 32",
                "answer": 704
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "25 x 33",
                "answer": 825
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "4 x 34",
                "answer": 136
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "24 x 86",
                "answer": 2064
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "56 x 7",
                "answer": 392
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "42 x 51",
                "answer": 2142
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "2 x 81",
                "answer": 162
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "32 x 87",
                "answer": 2784
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "67 x 52",
                "answer": 3484
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "76 x 13",
                "answer": 988
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "13 x 34",
                "answer": 442
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "98 x 19",
                "answer": 1862
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "86 x 18",
                "answer": 1548
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "55 x 90",
                "answer": 4950
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "95 x 39",
                "answer": 3705
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "87 x 87",
                "answer": 7569
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "4 x 12",
                "answer": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "72 x 9",
                "answer": 648
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "33 x 83",
                "answer": 2739
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "68 x 32",
                "answer": 2176
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "1 x 97",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "94 x 49",
                "answer": 4606
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "80 x 45",
                "answer": 3600
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "30 x 41",
                "answer": 1230
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "30 x 58",
                "answer": 1740
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "81 x 42",
                "answer": 3402
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "69 x 22",
                "answer": 1518
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "86 x 65",
                "answer": 5590
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "30 x 64",
                "answer": 1920
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "48 x 16",
                "answer": 768
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "91 x 82",
                "answer": 7462
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "66 x 19",
                "answer": 1254
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "9 x 75",
                "answer": 675
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "31 x 58",
                "answer": 1798
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "56 x 35",
                "answer": 1960
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "29 x 67",
                "answer": 1943
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "21 x 4",
                "answer": 84
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "24 x 48",
                "answer": 1152
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "48 x 61",
                "answer": 2928
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "89 x 53",
                "answer": 4717
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "21 x 5",
                "answer": 105
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "22 x 82",
                "answer": 1804
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "78 x 23",
                "answer": 1794
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "59 x 11",
                "answer": 649
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "32 x 34",
                "answer": 1088
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "4 x 85",
                "answer": 340
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "97 x 34",
                "answer": 3298
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "51 x 30",
                "answer": 1530
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "52 x 95",
                "answer": 4940
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "95 x 11",
                "answer": 1045
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "11 x 34",
                "answer": 374
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "68 x 54",
                "answer": 3672
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "18 x 87",
                "answer": 1566
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "10 x 1",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "26 x 12",
                "answer": 312
            }
        ]
    },
    "division": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "3572 : 38",
                "answer": 94
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "4845 : 95",
                "answer": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "6831 : 69",
                "answer": 99
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "456 : 57",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "5328 : 74",
                "answer": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "186 : 3",
                "answer": 62
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "2100 : 60",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "2660 : 28",
                "answer": 95
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "2479 : 37",
                "answer": 67
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "3312 : 72",
                "answer": 46
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "715 : 55",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "1800 : 25",
                "answer": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "4067 : 49",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "7742 : 98",
                "answer": 79
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "3024 : 63",
                "answer": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "6510 : 93",
                "answer": 70
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "234 : 3",
                "answer": 78
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "2240 : 64",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "3782 : 62",
                "answer": 61
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "1850 : 74",
                "answer": 25
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "6264 : 87",
                "answer": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "3942 : 54",
                "answer": 73
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "1235 : 19",
                "answer": 65
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "4560 : 48",
                "answer": 95
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "4988 : 86",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "220 : 4",
                "answer": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "1869 : 89",
                "answer": 21
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "336 : 28",
                "answer": 12
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "4753 : 49",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "2205 : 49",
                "answer": 45
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "1518 : 66",
                "answer": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "3157 : 77",
                "answer": 41
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "2880 : 96",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "783 : 87",
                "answer": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "1144 : 52",
                "answer": 22
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "1008 : 56",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "632 : 79",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "260 : 26",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "564 : 47",
                "answer": 12
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "1320 : 44",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "600 : 75",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "217 : 31",
                "answer": 7
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "5100 : 60",
                "answer": 85
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "549 : 9",
                "answer": 61
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "2006 : 59",
                "answer": 34
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "1602 : 18",
                "answer": 89
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "1470 : 30",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "2024 : 92",
                "answer": 22
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "216 : 6",
                "answer": 36
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "2784 : 58",
                "answer": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "256 : 4",
                "answer": 64
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "1824 : 32",
                "answer": 57
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "6120 : 85",
                "answer": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "6624 : 69",
                "answer": 96
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "1675 : 67",
                "answer": 25
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "1403 : 23",
                "answer": 61
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "2464 : 56",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "6120 : 72",
                "answer": 85
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "1720 : 20",
                "answer": 86
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "5952 : 93",
                "answer": 64
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "899 : 31",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "1320 : 22",
                "answer": 60
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "213 : 71",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "4558 : 53",
                "answer": 86
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "1209 : 13",
                "answer": 93
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "3496 : 92",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "108 : 18",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "408 : 8",
                "answer": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "1491 : 21",
                "answer": 71
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "7055 : 85",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "210 : 15",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "3157 : 77",
                "answer": 41
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "6640 : 80",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "2352 : 56",
                "answer": 42
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "1530 : 34",
                "answer": 45
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "1513 : 89",
                "answer": 17
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "4074 : 42",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "6525 : 87",
                "answer": 75
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "730 : 73",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "336 : 24",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "216 : 3",
                "answer": 72
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "3807 : 47",
                "answer": 81
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "138 : 23",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "216 : 12",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "2295 : 85",
                "answer": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "1184 : 32",
                "answer": 37
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "7680 : 80",
                "answer": 96
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "744 : 31",
                "answer": 24
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "4346 : 53",
                "answer": 82
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "6314 : 82",
                "answer": 77
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "4482 : 83",
                "answer": 54
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "1444 : 76",
                "answer": 19
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "168 : 3",
                "answer": 56
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "2698 : 71",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "891 : 11",
                "answer": 81
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "4221 : 63",
                "answer": 67
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "3977 : 41",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "1950 : 30",
                "answer": 65
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "4015 : 73",
                "answer": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "75 : 5",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "6256 : 68",
                "answer": 92
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "1260 : 70",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "1274 : 91",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "1200 : 20",
                "answer": 60
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "3735 : 45",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "2688 : 32",
                "answer": 84
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "1785 : 35",
                "answer": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "2500 : 50",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "1071 : 51",
                "answer": 21
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "1378 : 53",
                "answer": 26
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "3500 : 35",
                "answer": 100
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "5292 : 84",
                "answer": 63
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "4225 : 65",
                "answer": 65
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "3354 : 86",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "286 : 26",
                "answer": 11
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "68 : 17",
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "261 : 3",
                "answer": 87
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "7 : 1",
                "answer": 7
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "6864 : 88",
                "answer": 78
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "3190 : 55",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "748 : 11",
                "answer": 68
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "1494 : 18",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "3105 : 69",
                "answer": 45
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "4221 : 63",
                "answer": 67
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "3248 : 56",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "994 : 71",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "960 : 60",
                "answer": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "2356 : 38",
                "answer": 62
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "6557 : 79",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "483 : 7",
                "answer": 69
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "8360 : 88",
                "answer": 95
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "3074 : 53",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "3120 : 60",
                "answer": 52
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "1311 : 69",
                "answer": 19
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "4092 : 93",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "5767 : 73",
                "answer": 79
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "1131 : 29",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "5130 : 57",
                "answer": 90
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "2209 : 47",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "1720 : 40",
                "answer": 43
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "1870 : 34",
                "answer": 55
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "3360 : 96",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "249 : 83",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "300 : 6",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "4558 : 53",
                "answer": 86
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "7275 : 75",
                "answer": 97
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "874 : 46",
                "answer": 19
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "4042 : 47",
                "answer": 86
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "4158 : 66",
                "answer": 63
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "3528 : 72",
                "answer": 49
            }
        ]
    },
    "fractions": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "3/ 6 + 10/ 3 + 5/ 8",
                "answer": "107/24"
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "8/ 7 : 2/ 4 x 3/ 5",
                "answer": "48/35"
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "3/ 9 : 3/ 3 x 10/ 4 - 10/ 7",
                "answer": "-25/42"
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "1/ 2 : 3/ 9 + 6/ 10",
                "answer": "21/10"
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "2/ 5 : 1/ 6 + 4/ 1",
                "answer": "32/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "9/ 7 + 1/ 9 x 1/ 3 : 7/ 6",
                "answer": "83/63"
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "9/ 6 : 4/ 9 x 2/ 10",
                "answer": "27/40"
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "4/ 4 : 7/ 1 : 8/ 9 + 1/ 4",
                "answer": "23/56"
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "9/ 4 + 10/ 7",
                "answer": "103/28"
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "5/ 1 x 2/ 1 x 6/ 4",
                "answer": "15"
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "3/ 2 - 9/ 3 : 3/ 8",
                "answer": "-13/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "2/ 9 x 7/ 5 : 1/ 3 - 2/ 5",
                "answer": "8/15"
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "6/ 9 : 10/ 3 x 9/ 7 x 8/ 5",
                "answer": "72/175"
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "4/ 5 - 1/ 1 + 2/ 4 + 5/ 8",
                "answer": "37/40"
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "10/ 10 + 3/ 10 - 1/ 7 + 10/ 7",
                "answer": "181/70"
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "9/ 6 + 5/ 2 : 1/ 3 + 4/ 10",
                "answer": "47/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "2/ 10 - 2/ 3 + 7/ 2",
                "answer": "91/30"
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "2/ 2 x 6/ 2 + 3/ 9 + 2/ 7",
                "answer": "76/21"
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "3/ 8 x 9/ 10 + 2/ 4",
                "answer": "67/80"
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "9/ 4 : 3/ 4 + 6/ 8",
                "answer": "15/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "7/ 9 + 9/ 2",
                "answer": "95/18"
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "1/ 4 + 10/ 7 x 5/ 3",
                "answer": "221/84"
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "1/ 4 x 2/ 2",
                "answer": "1/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "3/ 6 x 8/ 1 - 10/ 5 x 5/ 8",
                "answer": "11/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "5/ 7 + 4/ 1 + 4/ 7 : 6/ 3",
                "answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "3/ 9 : 5/ 6",
                "answer": "2/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "6/ 1 x 9/ 2 : 7/ 4",
                "answer": "108/7"
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "10/ 7 - 10/ 8 x 1/ 8",
                "answer": "285/224"
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "2/ 9 : 8/ 10 - 6/ 9 : 3/ 9",
                "answer": "-31/18"
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "7/ 3 + 5/ 6",
                "answer": "19/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "6/ 6 : 1/ 5 - 10/ 1 - 7/ 6",
                "answer": "-37/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "1/ 8 : 1/ 8",
                "answer": "1"
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "3/ 2 : 3/ 5",
                "answer": "5/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "9/ 3 : 10/ 5",
                "answer": "3/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "9/ 9 - 6/ 3",
                "answer": "-1"
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "7/ 3 + 9/ 3 + 3/ 2",
                "answer": "41/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "2/ 1 : 7/ 2 - 5/ 9 + 8/ 7",
                "answer": "73/63"
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "2/ 7 x 1/ 7 x 7/ 8",
                "answer": "1/28"
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "9/ 10 + 9/ 7 - 4/ 1 + 6/ 7",
                "answer": "-67/70"
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "9/ 3 x 3/ 6 - 10/ 6 x 9/ 9",
                "answer": "-1/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "9/ 8 : 4/ 10 + 7/ 7 x 1/ 1",
                "answer": "61/16"
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "7/ 7 - 9/ 3",
                "answer": "-2"
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "4/ 8 x 7/ 10",
                "answer": "7/20"
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "4/ 7 : 2/ 10 - 5/ 7",
                "answer": "15/7"
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "10/ 6 : 9/ 7 - 3/ 9",
                "answer": "26/27"
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "3/ 7 : 1/ 5 - 1/ 4",
                "answer": "53/28"
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "8/ 2 x 6/ 2",
                "answer": "12"
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "4/ 8 : 10/ 3 x 1/ 1",
                "answer": "3/20"
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "4/ 6 : 4/ 4",
                "answer": "2/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "3/ 8 x 10/ 4 + 6/ 3",
                "answer": "47/16"
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "1/ 6 + 3/ 5",
                "answer": "23/30"
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "5/ 8 : 5/ 8 x 9/ 6 : 10/ 6",
                "answer": "9/10"
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "4/ 5 - 8/ 3 + 2/ 2 x 7/ 4",
                "answer": "-7/60"
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "1/ 6 + 1/ 10",
                "answer": "4/15"
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "9/ 5 : 3/ 5 + 10/ 6",
                "answer": "14/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "1/ 5 : 7/ 8",
                "answer": "8/35"
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "7/ 7 + 4/ 1",
                "answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "8/ 10 : 2/ 8",
                "answer": "16/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "4/ 2 - 9/ 8",
                "answer": "7/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "10/ 8 + 7/ 8 : 1/ 9 + 4/ 3",
                "answer": "251/24"
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "6/ 5 : 10/ 10",
                "answer": "6/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "3/ 1 x 9/ 8",
                "answer": "27/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "2/ 2 - 4/ 8",
                "answer": "1/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "4/ 6 - 6/ 9 - 3/ 2",
                "answer": "-3/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "9/ 3 - 8/ 3",
                "answer": "1/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "1/ 3 : 5/ 6 - 9/ 1",
                "answer": "-43/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "10/ 7 x 10/ 10 - 5/ 2 - 2/ 7",
                "answer": "-19/14"
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "4/ 9 - 3/ 3",
                "answer": "-5/9"
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "6/ 7 + 9/ 8 - 5/ 8",
                "answer": "19/14"
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "6/ 3 : 2/ 9 - 2/ 2 - 1/ 8",
                "answer": "63/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "2/ 3 : 1/ 4 x 5/ 3",
                "answer": "40/9"
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "9/ 4 : 6/ 10",
                "answer": "15/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "10/ 5 x 3/ 5",
                "answer": "6/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "5/ 8 - 4/ 4",
                "answer": "-3/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "3/ 2 : 1/ 2",
                "answer": "3"
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "5/ 4 : 6/ 5 : 3/ 6 + 5/ 9",
                "answer": "95/36"
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "4/ 10 - 3/ 3 x 9/ 10",
                "answer": "-1/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "6/ 5 - 5/ 7",
                "answer": "17/35"
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "6/ 1 - 2/ 8 + 4/ 9 : 7/ 5",
                "answer": "1529/252"
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "6/ 10 x 5/ 4",
                "answer": "3/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "6/ 3 x 1/ 6 - 3/ 5 x 3/ 10",
                "answer": "23/150"
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "9/ 10 x 9/ 1 : 3/ 8 : 10/ 2",
                "answer": "108/25"
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "4/ 2 : 9/ 6 + 8/ 1 - 10/ 8",
                "answer": "97/12"
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "10/ 2 + 4/ 1 x 7/ 3",
                "answer": "43/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "3/ 6 - 8/ 2 - 1/ 3",
                "answer": "-23/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "2/ 7 : 8/ 5",
                "answer": "5/28"
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "4/ 10 x 1/ 3 : 3/ 4",
                "answer": "8/45"
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "9/ 2 x 7/ 8 + 3/ 6 : 4/ 3",
                "answer": "69/16"
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "8/ 9 + 2/ 10 - 8/ 10",
                "answer": "13/45"
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "5/ 5 x 6/ 2",
                "answer": "3"
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "2/ 4 - 6/ 9",
                "answer": "-1/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "2/ 6 : 2/ 7",
                "answer": "7/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "8/ 6 + 8/ 1 x 5/ 9 + 2/ 4",
                "answer": "113/18"
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "10/ 7 + 10/ 6 - 9/ 7 : 2/ 1",
                "answer": "103/42"
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "6/ 8 x 10/ 4",
                "answer": "15/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "1/ 2 x 1/ 9",
                "answer": "1/18"
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "9/ 8 : 4/ 5 x 1/ 7",
                "answer": "45/224"
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "4/ 9 + 9/ 10 - 1/ 4",
                "answer": "197/180"
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "5/ 10 - 5/ 6 - 7/ 1 x 10/ 7",
                "answer": "-31/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "4/ 8 - 6/ 10 + 7/ 9 x 1/ 4",
                "answer": "17/180"
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "4/ 6 + 3/ 7 - 9/ 7",
                "answer": "-4/21"
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "10/ 8 - 4/ 1",
                "answer": "-11/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "8/ 3 - 6/ 10 : 7/ 9",
                "answer": "199/105"
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "6/ 1 + 10/ 2",
                "answer": "11"
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "9/ 9 + 9/ 6 x 6/ 4",
                "answer": "13/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "7/ 10 : 10/ 8 x 2/ 2 x 3/ 3",
                "answer": "14/25"
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "1/ 6 + 9/ 6 x 5/ 5 + 4/ 6",
                "answer": "7/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "3/ 4 x 9/ 4",
                "answer": "27/16"
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "2/ 1 + 8/ 7 - 6/ 9 x 8/ 8",
                "answer": "52/21"
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "6/ 6 x 1/ 2 : 8/ 2",
                "answer": "1/8"
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "8/ 9 - 4/ 7 - 2/ 4 - 10/ 4",
                "answer": "-169/63"
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "4/ 4 - 9/ 1",
                "answer": "-8"
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "6/ 8 - 5/ 3 x 6/ 4",
                "answer": "-7/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "10/ 5 + 9/ 3 x 6/ 1 - 4/ 5",
                "answer": "96/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "10/ 2 : 6/ 2 x 5/ 1",
                "answer": "25/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "2/ 8 + 9/ 7 x 4/ 6",
                "answer": "31/28"
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "3/ 7 + 6/ 10 - 8/ 10 - 4/ 2",
                "answer": "-62/35"
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "7/ 5 + 6/ 2 : 8/ 2 : 9/ 5",
                "answer": "109/60"
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "1/ 4 + 1/ 2 : 8/ 5 : 4/ 7",
                "answer": "51/64"
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "1/ 2 : 2/ 7",
                "answer": "7/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "4/ 10 x 8/ 4 + 6/ 2 x 5/ 10",
                "answer": "23/10"
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "8/ 3 + 4/ 2 x 1/ 5 - 2/ 5",
                "answer": "8/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "9/ 4 : 3/ 7",
                "answer": "21/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "9/ 6 - 8/ 7 x 4/ 4 + 4/ 10",
                "answer": "53/70"
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "3/ 10 x 2/ 2 + 6/ 6 : 7/ 1",
                "answer": "31/70"
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "5/ 5 + 8/ 9",
                "answer": "17/9"
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "5/ 7 : 7/ 9 x 2/ 8 : 2/ 1",
                "answer": "45/392"
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "3/ 3 : 2/ 9 + 5/ 6",
                "answer": "16/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "1/ 6 x 1/ 4",
                "answer": "1/24"
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "1/ 9 : 9/ 3",
                "answer": "1/27"
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "3/ 3 + 4/ 9",
                "answer": "13/9"
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "8/ 6 + 2/ 8 - 4/ 6 + 8/ 2",
                "answer": "59/12"
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "8/ 4 x 10/ 6",
                "answer": "10/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "7/ 3 + 3/ 10 x 4/ 9 x 1/ 6",
                "answer": "106/45"
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "4/ 8 x 6/ 5 : 10/ 10",
                "answer": "3/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "7/ 7 + 5/ 10 - 10/ 5",
                "answer": "-1/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "8/ 6 x 7/ 8",
                "answer": "7/6"
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "7/ 2 + 4/ 9 : 8/ 10 x 10/ 5",
                "answer": "83/18"
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "9/ 1 : 3/ 3 x 4/ 9",
                "answer": "4"
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "2/ 4 x 3/ 7",
                "answer": "3/14"
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "2/ 10 : 9/ 6 + 10/ 10 : 8/ 7",
                "answer": "121/120"
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "6/ 3 x 7/ 9 : 1/ 5",
                "answer": "70/9"
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "6/ 6 + 9/ 5",
                "answer": "14/5"
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "6/ 6 : 2/ 10 - 2/ 6",
                "answer": "14/3"
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "4/ 8 : 5/ 8 x 2/ 10 : 2/ 3",
                "answer": "6/25"
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "2/ 8 - 9/ 6 : 1/ 10 + 8/ 6",
                "answer": "-161/12"
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "1/ 6 + 5/ 8 - 7/ 3",
                "answer": "-37/24"
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "5/ 6 : 2/ 3 x 7/ 7 + 8/ 1",
                "answer": "37/4"
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "8/ 2 + 10/ 4",
                "answer": "13/2"
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "5/ 5 + 6/ 1 + 10/ 7",
                "answer": "59/7"
            }
        ]
    },
    "root_squared": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "\u221a1024",
                "answer": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "\u221a196",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "\u221a729",
                "answer": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "\u221a169",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "\u221a1089",
                "answer": 33
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "\u221a1936",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "\u221a121",
                "answer": 11
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "\u221a256",
                "answer": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "\u221a144",
                "answer": 12
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "\u221a529",
                "answer": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "\u221a36",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "\u221a1681",
                "answer": 41
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "\u221a25",
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "\u221a625",
                "answer": 25
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "\u221a400",
                "answer": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "\u221a961",
                "answer": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "\u221a961",
                "answer": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "\u221a256",
                "answer": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "\u221a16",
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "\u221a9",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "\u221a1444",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "\u221a2209",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "\u221a1521",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "\u221a1936",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "\u221a2500",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "\u221a196",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "\u221a324",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "\u221a36",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "\u221a4",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "\u221a1444",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "\u221a1225",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "\u221a676",
                "answer": 26
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "\u221a529",
                "answer": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "\u221a1600",
                "answer": 40
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "\u221a1936",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "\u221a100",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "\u221a289",
                "answer": 17
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "\u221a100",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "\u221a784",
                "answer": 28
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "\u221a196",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "\u221a1764",
                "answer": 42
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "\u221a25",
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "\u221a1225",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "\u221a169",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "\u221a625",
                "answer": 25
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "\u221a1225",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "\u221a100",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "\u221a2500",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "\u221a169",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "\u221a196",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "\u221a961",
                "answer": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "\u221a2500",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "\u221a169",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "\u221a2500",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "\u221a1444",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "\u221a36",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "\u221a81",
                "answer": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "\u221a729",
                "answer": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "\u221a4",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "\u221a400",
                "answer": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "\u221a2116",
                "answer": 46
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "\u221a961",
                "answer": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "\u221a676",
                "answer": 26
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "\u221a81",
                "answer": 9
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "\u221a1521",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "\u221a36",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "\u221a16",
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "\u221a1600",
                "answer": 40
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "\u221a1849",
                "answer": 43
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "\u221a1521",
                "answer": 39
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "\u221a1444",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "\u221a324",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "\u221a1369",
                "answer": 37
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "\u221a1089",
                "answer": 33
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "\u221a1024",
                "answer": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "\u221a1089",
                "answer": 33
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "\u221a9",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "\u221a529",
                "answer": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "\u221a1089",
                "answer": 33
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "\u221a576",
                "answer": 24
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "\u221a144",
                "answer": 12
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "\u221a100",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "\u221a2401",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "\u221a9",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "\u221a2116",
                "answer": 46
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "\u221a25",
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "\u221a1225",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "\u221a961",
                "answer": 31
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "\u221a1156",
                "answer": 34
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "\u221a1024",
                "answer": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "\u221a2209",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "\u221a400",
                "answer": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "\u221a1764",
                "answer": 42
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "\u221a196",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "\u221a400",
                "answer": 20
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "\u221a1296",
                "answer": 36
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "\u221a900",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "\u221a1936",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "\u221a1369",
                "answer": 37
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "\u221a1849",
                "answer": 43
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "\u221a1444",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "\u221a169",
                "answer": 13
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "\u221a2025",
                "answer": 45
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "\u221a1369",
                "answer": 37
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "\u221a2209",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "\u221a1225",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "\u221a324",
                "answer": 18
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "\u221a225",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "\u221a361",
                "answer": 19
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "\u221a1936",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "\u221a25",
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "\u221a2500",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "\u221a64",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "\u221a484",
                "answer": 22
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "\u221a1681",
                "answer": 41
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "\u221a841",
                "answer": 29
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "\u221a784",
                "answer": 28
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "\u221a49",
                "answer": 7
            }
        ]
    },
    "exponents": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "2^17",
                "answer": 131072
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "10^16",
                "answer": 10000000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "18^7",
                "answer": 612220032
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "42^14",
                "answer": 53148384174432398229504
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "12^12",
                "answer": 8916100448256
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "32^1",
                "answer": 32
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "17^16",
                "answer": 48661191875666868481
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "17^5",
                "answer": 1419857
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "21^15",
                "answer": 68122318582951682301
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "46^9",
                "answer": 922190162669056
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "9^8",
                "answer": 43046721
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "29^6",
                "answer": 594823321
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "3^12",
                "answer": 531441
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "37^15",
                "answer": 333446267951815307088493
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "48^9",
                "answer": 1352605460594688
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "24^11",
                "answer": 1521681143169024
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "32^10",
                "answer": 1125899906842624
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "12^18",
                "answer": 26623333280885243904
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "9^15",
                "answer": 205891132094649
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "15^15",
                "answer": 437893890380859375
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "30^1",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "34^5",
                "answer": 45435424
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "46^20",
                "answer": 1799519816997495209117766334283776
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "9^18",
                "answer": 150094635296999121
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "41^8",
                "answer": 7984925229121
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "23^12",
                "answer": 21914624432020321
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "46^9",
                "answer": 922190162669056
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "8^3",
                "answer": 512
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "4^10",
                "answer": 1048576
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "1^8",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "18^15",
                "answer": 6746640616477458432
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "5^9",
                "answer": 1953125
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "1^13",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "26^17",
                "answer": 1133827315385150725554176
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "4^5",
                "answer": 1024
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "26^19",
                "answer": 766467265200361890474622976
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "29^12",
                "answer": 353814783205469041
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "34^4",
                "answer": 1336336
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "14^3",
                "answer": 2744
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "44^5",
                "answer": 164916224
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "11^8",
                "answer": 214358881
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "47^18",
                "answer": 1252453015827223091648143056289
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "8^4",
                "answer": 4096
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "35^16",
                "answer": 5070942774902496337890625
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "3^18",
                "answer": 387420489
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "32^20",
                "answer": 1267650600228229401496703205376
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "42^16",
                "answer": 93753749683698750476845056
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "14^17",
                "answer": 30491346729331195904
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "44^8",
                "answer": 14048223625216
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "24^14",
                "answer": 21035720123168587776
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "40^6",
                "answer": 4096000000
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "11^13",
                "answer": 34522712143931
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "25^9",
                "answer": 3814697265625
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "2^3",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "7^5",
                "answer": 16807
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "50^19",
                "answer": 190734863281250000000000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "35^3",
                "answer": 42875
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "8^2",
                "answer": 64
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "13^20",
                "answer": 19004963774880799438801
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "49^9",
                "answer": 1628413597910449
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "19^12",
                "answer": 2213314919066161
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "39^11",
                "answer": 317475837322472439
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "5^14",
                "answer": 6103515625
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "7^7",
                "answer": 823543
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "6^2",
                "answer": 36
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "35^16",
                "answer": 5070942774902496337890625
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "50^3",
                "answer": 125000
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "4^1",
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "12^19",
                "answer": 319479999370622926848
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "27^18",
                "answer": 58149737003040059690390169
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "6^2",
                "answer": 36
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "36^5",
                "answer": 60466176
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "9^18",
                "answer": 150094635296999121
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "28^3",
                "answer": 21952
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "9^6",
                "answer": 531441
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "34^20",
                "answer": 4261655511456885005249781170176
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "16^15",
                "answer": 1152921504606846976
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "11^4",
                "answer": 14641
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "41^12",
                "answer": 22563490300366186081
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "19^18",
                "answer": 104127350297911241532841
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "46^3",
                "answer": 97336
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "5^14",
                "answer": 6103515625
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "49^14",
                "answer": 459986536544739960976801
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "18^13",
                "answer": 20822964865671168
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "1^6",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "19^5",
                "answer": 2476099
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "36^18",
                "answer": 10314424798490535546171949056
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "10^14",
                "answer": 100000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "35^3",
                "answer": 42875
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "50^8",
                "answer": 39062500000000
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "13^18",
                "answer": 112455406951957393129
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "6^20",
                "answer": 3656158440062976
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "3^8",
                "answer": 6561
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "39^15",
                "answer": 734461618571137961752599
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "41^9",
                "answer": 327381934393961
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "40^12",
                "answer": 16777216000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "25^3",
                "answer": 15625
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "7^9",
                "answer": 40353607
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "7^2",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "5^17",
                "answer": 762939453125
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "26^9",
                "answer": 5429503678976
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "44^16",
                "answer": 197352587024076973231046656
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "3^6",
                "answer": 729
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "14^16",
                "answer": 2177953337809371136
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "27^13",
                "answer": 4052555153018976267
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "13^16",
                "answer": 665416609183179841
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "16^13",
                "answer": 4503599627370496
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "50^1",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "27^1",
                "answer": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "34^5",
                "answer": 45435424
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "43^6",
                "answer": 6321363049
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "16^15",
                "answer": 1152921504606846976
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "18^19",
                "answer": 708235345355337676357632
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "36^17",
                "answer": 286511799958070431838109696
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "38^3",
                "answer": 54872
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "34^9",
                "answer": 60716992766464
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "36^3",
                "answer": 46656
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "39^7",
                "answer": 137231006679
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "25^9",
                "answer": 3814697265625
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "29^9",
                "answer": 14507145975869
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "31^2",
                "answer": 961
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "25^17",
                "answer": 582076609134674072265625
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "36^20",
                "answer": 13367494538843734067838845976576
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "12^14",
                "answer": 1283918464548864
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "4^4",
                "answer": 256
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "31^15",
                "answer": 23465261991844685929951
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "41^15",
                "answer": 1555098314991537910888601
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "6^17",
                "answer": 16926659444736
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "37^13",
                "answer": 243569224216081305397
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "2^9",
                "answer": 512
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "8^1",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "36^6",
                "answer": 2176782336
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "16^20",
                "answer": 1208925819614629174706176
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "21^19",
                "answer": 13248496640331026125580781
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "16^1",
                "answer": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "28^19",
                "answer": 3133304450029408431470804992
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "1^15",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "39^11",
                "answer": 317475837322472439
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "43^12",
                "answer": 39959630797262576401
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "38^2",
                "answer": 1444
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "2^3",
                "answer": 8
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "30^14",
                "answer": 478296900000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "11^6",
                "answer": 1771561
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "1^20",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "4^13",
                "answer": 67108864
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "9^12",
                "answer": 282429536481
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "18^14",
                "answer": 374813367582081024
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "41^16",
                "answer": 63759030914653054346432641
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "4^18",
                "answer": 68719476736
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "36^5",
                "answer": 60466176
            }
        ]
    },
    "negative": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "(40) x (-28) - (-20)",
                "answer": -1100
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "(56) - (-32) - (37)",
                "answer": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "(-18) + (94) : (14) + (4)",
                "answer": -7
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "(-94) x (67) + (-24) : (33)",
                "answer": -6299
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "(39) : (-62) + (28) : (82)",
                "answer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "(-51) : (22) : (-50)",
                "answer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "(-69) + (84) x (-70) - (28)",
                "answer": -5977
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "(33) : (-70) + (77)",
                "answer": 77
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "(54) : (41) + (-80) x (68)",
                "answer": -5439
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "(-43) + (-28) : (48) - (-88)",
                "answer": 44
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "(58) : (-95)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "(-3) + (31) - (-41)",
                "answer": 69
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "(37) x (-14) x (-4)",
                "answer": 2072
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "(34) x (81) - (-61)",
                "answer": 2815
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "(92) - (98)",
                "answer": -6
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "(-87) + (-61) : (97) - (-79)",
                "answer": -9
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "(87) + (-64) + (40) : (-37)",
                "answer": 22
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "(67) : (-77)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "(-66) + (55) : (-42)",
                "answer": -67
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "(84) : (-69) : (-28)",
                "answer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "(-8) x (-6) - (55)",
                "answer": -7
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "(-67) + (-21)",
                "answer": -88
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "(-100) : (35) : (-47) x (-86)",
                "answer": -5
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "(83) x (44) + (90)",
                "answer": 3742
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "(95) + (-20) : (-86)",
                "answer": 95
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "(-58) - (-40) - (-46)",
                "answer": 28
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "(70) : (13) + (12)",
                "answer": 17
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "(-92) x (-32) : (-7)",
                "answer": -421
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "(67) - (99) + (40) + (18)",
                "answer": 26
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "(-84) : (98)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "(-45) x (-44)",
                "answer": 1980
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "(52) + (60)",
                "answer": 112
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "(89) + (67) + (11)",
                "answer": 167
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "(91) x (67)",
                "answer": 6097
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "(11) - (19) + (-89) - (17)",
                "answer": -114
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "(-29) x (50)",
                "answer": -1450
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "(-80) - (1) : (25)",
                "answer": -80
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "(-45) x (-88) - (92)",
                "answer": 3868
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "(17) + (-71) x (-19) x (33)",
                "answer": 44534
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "(-40) - (39) : (-78)",
                "answer": -40
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "(-76) + (-84) : (27) + (93)",
                "answer": 14
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "(29) - (50) : (43) + (-95)",
                "answer": -67
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "(-19) : (2) : (-6)",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "(29) + (-44) - (-22) - (63)",
                "answer": -56
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "(-95) + (-31)",
                "answer": -126
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "(-84) : (9) x (37)",
                "answer": -345
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "(-58) - (85) x (-37) x (-4)",
                "answer": -12638
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "(-85) + (-28)",
                "answer": -113
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "(-12) x (-100) + (-25)",
                "answer": 1175
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "(-94) x (50) x (28) - (10)",
                "answer": -131610
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "(-56) x (-32) - (31) + (38)",
                "answer": 1799
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "(-57) : (-50)",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "(24) : (-58) + (84)",
                "answer": 84
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "(-12) - (-62) x (14)",
                "answer": 856
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "(55) : (-71) - (72) x (21)",
                "answer": -1513
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "(87) : (-62)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "(89) - (-72) - (-17) - (63)",
                "answer": 115
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "(-25) - (-95)",
                "answer": 70
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "(-83) - (-8) + (-45) x (-86)",
                "answer": 3795
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "(-42) x (-77) : (-96)",
                "answer": -34
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "(-97) - (-49) - (-55) : (-47)",
                "answer": -49
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "(-28) x (32) : (-84) x (-85)",
                "answer": -907
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "(-40) : (2) x (-47) - (-42)",
                "answer": 982
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "(68) x (-68) : (-2) : (-79)",
                "answer": -29
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "(-24) x (91) : (83)",
                "answer": -26
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "(-71) : (22) x (95)",
                "answer": -307
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "(4) + (30) x (43) x (21)",
                "answer": 27094
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "(53) : (71) x (65)",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "(28) : (21)",
                "answer": 1
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "(35) - (98) x (-1)",
                "answer": 133
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "(52) + (-58) - (97) - (91)",
                "answer": -194
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "(-48) - (-94) x (-33) + (84)",
                "answer": -3066
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "(-40) + (-82) + (66)",
                "answer": -56
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "(65) + (59) x (-22) x (-100)",
                "answer": 129865
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "(-15) - (65) - (46)",
                "answer": -126
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "(-91) : (-11) : (91) + (-51)",
                "answer": -51
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "(-83) : (-16)",
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "(-31) - (-34) x (70) + (-74)",
                "answer": 2275
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "(-21) + (51) + (-62)",
                "answer": -32
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "(92) + (35) + (52) : (72)",
                "answer": 128
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "(90) : (55)",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "(27) : (24) x (-53)",
                "answer": -60
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "(-50) x (97)",
                "answer": -4850
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "(-100) + (31) + (-72) + (-15)",
                "answer": -156
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "(-47) - (20) - (-75) x (-67)",
                "answer": -5092
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "(2) + (-100)",
                "answer": -98
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "(53) - (-94) : (92)",
                "answer": 54
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "(71) : (-99)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "(-13) x (-93) : (94) + (-59)",
                "answer": -46
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "(65) - (-46) - (-89)",
                "answer": 200
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "(-43) : (-18) x (-12)",
                "answer": -29
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "(-70) + (87) - (51)",
                "answer": -34
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "(56) - (74) x (41) : (-2)",
                "answer": 1573
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "(60) - (-86) : (50) - (-37)",
                "answer": 99
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "(-67) : (88)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "(67) : (57) : (3)",
                "answer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "(83) : (54)",
                "answer": 2
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "(-68) x (10) : (12)",
                "answer": -57
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "(-39) + (-52) x (52) : (1)",
                "answer": -2743
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "(64) : (-53) + (73) - (-28)",
                "answer": 100
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "(-79) + (61) : (34) - (40)",
                "answer": -117
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "(-56) : (-51) - (-15)",
                "answer": 16
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "(63) x (-81)",
                "answer": -5103
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "(98) : (-98) x (97)",
                "answer": -97
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "(-63) x (-99) x (85) - (-60)",
                "answer": 530205
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "(51) x (12) x (-11) x (76)",
                "answer": -511632
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "(-58) : (56) - (-84)",
                "answer": 83
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "(-74) - (-1) - (18)",
                "answer": -91
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "(22) : (94) - (-73) x (82)",
                "answer": 5986
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "(-22) + (-78) x (-36)",
                "answer": 2786
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "(-26) + (89) x (95) : (93)",
                "answer": 65
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "(41) x (86)",
                "answer": 3526
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "(-32) + (55) : (27) : (81)",
                "answer": -32
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "(21) x (-9) + (-69) - (-31)",
                "answer": -227
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "(17) x (-21) - (-75) x (63)",
                "answer": 4368
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "(-67) + (-41) : (10)",
                "answer": -71
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "(41) + (37)",
                "answer": 78
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "(9) + (1)",
                "answer": 10
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "(85) + (16)",
                "answer": 101
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "(-83) - (32) x (-37)",
                "answer": 1101
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "(-77) : (73) + (-10)",
                "answer": -11
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "(-69) : (-20)",
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "(40) : (-79) : (-83)",
                "answer": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "(-51) - (-2) x (94)",
                "answer": 137
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "(-20) + (-62)",
                "answer": -82
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "(-59) - (-19) : (-10)",
                "answer": -61
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "(34) - (-30) + (-17)",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "(-21) + (-92)",
                "answer": -113
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "(79) - (-61) - (-49)",
                "answer": 189
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "(95) - (-81) x (-36) x (-77)",
                "answer": 224627
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "(-9) x (37) - (-57) - (-58)",
                "answer": -218
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "(-100) + (84) : (-14)",
                "answer": -106
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "(32) - (-91) x (82) x (51)",
                "answer": 380594
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "(-89) x (28) + (-14)",
                "answer": -2506
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "(-36) - (93) : (-44)",
                "answer": -34
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "(57) : (-57) - (-29) x (-70)",
                "answer": -2031
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "(-11) - (53)",
                "answer": -64
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "(-98) - (52)",
                "answer": -150
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "(2) : (-84) x (-76) x (-59)",
                "answer": -107
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "(34) : (-39) x (-56)",
                "answer": 49
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "(49) x (-22) x (-68)",
                "answer": 73304
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "(-44) - (-8) + (100) x (14)",
                "answer": 1364
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "(69) - (28) + (83)",
                "answer": 124
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "(-13) - (-90) : (-18)",
                "answer": -18
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "(62) : (-73)",
                "answer": -1
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "(-53) - (-87)",
                "answer": 34
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "(64) x (44) + (94)",
                "answer": 2910
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "(-23) x (-53) x (24)",
                "answer": 29256
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "(-41) x (-13)",
                "answer": 533
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "(9) - (34) : (-58)",
                "answer": 10
            }
        ]
    },
    "mixed": {
        "questions": [
            {
                "id": 1,
                "question": "18 x 67 + (-16) - (-81) : (35) x (-35)",
                "answer": 1109
            },
            {
                "id": 2,
                "question": "3731 : 41 + 905 + 276 + (-45) + (-13) + (75) - (26)",
                "answer": 1263
            },
            {
                "id": 3,
                "question": "1887 : 37 + (24) : (-7) : (-49)",
                "answer": 51
            },
            {
                "id": 4,
                "question": "\u221a784 + 42^17 + (-71) - (77) x (81) x (38)",
                "answer": 62750756861693
            },
            {
                "id": 5,
                "question": "20 x 31 + 244 : 61 + \u221a400 + 639 - 341",
                "answer": 650
            },
            {
                "id": 6,
                "question": "6/ 3 - 3/ 3 + 58 x 97 + \u221a1521 + 16^20",
                "answer": 1099511633403
            },
            {
                "id": 7,
                "question": "45 x 98 + 49^16 + 315 - 796 + (-90) x (-79) + (-35)",
                "answer": 1104427674243920646305310205
            },
            {
                "id": 8,
                "question": "630 + 666 + 8245 : 85",
                "answer": 1393
            },
            {
                "id": 9,
                "question": "477 - 114 + 286 + 331 + \u221a729",
                "answer": 1007
            },
            {
                "id": 10,
                "question": "3/ 6 - 7/ 4 + (-81) x (14) x (85) - (28) + 5520 : 60",
                "answer": -96327
            },
            {
                "id": 11,
                "question": "541 + 86 + 6/ 7 + 3/ 1 + 2822 : 34",
                "answer": 714
            },
            {
                "id": 12,
                "question": "945 : 45 + 8/ 5 + 10/ 8 + 31 x 70 + 520 - 146",
                "answer": 2568
            },
            {
                "id": 13,
                "question": "3686 : 38 + 687 - 982 + 500 + 209 + 43 x 92",
                "answer": 4467
            },
            {
                "id": 14,
                "question": "9 x 53 + 719 + 652",
                "answer": 1848
            },
            {
                "id": 15,
                "question": "608 - 876 + 67 x 16 + 5/ 7 + 5/ 9",
                "answer": 805
            },
            {
                "id": 16,
                "question": "44 x 58 + 1^6",
                "answer": 2553
            },
            {
                "id": 17,
                "question": "6 x 92 + 4^1 + \u221a121 + 10/ 7 - 8/ 2",
                "answer": 567
            },
            {
                "id": 18,
                "question": "674 - 125 + 33^2",
                "answer": 1638
            },
            {
                "id": 19,
                "question": "\u221a256 + 330 + 649",
                "answer": 35
            },
            {
                "id": 20,
                "question": "3159 : 81 + 316 - 35",
                "answer": 320
            },
            {
                "id": 21,
                "question": "530 - 784 + 736 + 613 + 25^12 + 182 : 26",
                "answer": 59604644775391728
            },
            {
                "id": 22,
                "question": "1/ 3 x 7/ 7 x 5/ 7 + (-86) + (89) + (9) + 433 - 771",
                "answer": -326
            },
            {
                "id": 23,
                "question": "2/ 9 + 8/ 6 x 3/ 2 - 4/ 5 + (90) x (23) x (2) x (8) + 82 x 20",
                "answer": 34761
            },
            {
                "id": 24,
                "question": "44^10 + 80 - 969 + (44) + (-10) x (41)",
                "answer": 27197360938416921
            },
            {
                "id": 25,
                "question": "964 - 568 + \u221a1024 + 2/ 3 - 7/ 4 + 5/ 6 : 4/ 9 + (63) - (56) - (-21) : (78)",
                "answer": 428
            },
            {
                "id": 26,
                "question": "669 - 360 + 284 + 464",
                "answer": 1057
            },
            {
                "id": 27,
                "question": "(-76) x (14) + (-85) + 19^3 + 1/ 9 : 8/ 3 : 8/ 4",
                "answer": 5710
            },
            {
                "id": 28,
                "question": "275 - 160 + \u221a25",
                "answer": 120
            },
            {
                "id": 29,
                "question": "5355 : 63 + 6^10 + 19 x 12 + 586 - 44",
                "answer": 60467031
            },
            {
                "id": 30,
                "question": "(-74) : (-4) x (17) + 653 - 841 + 8 x 48",
                "answer": 510
            },
            {
                "id": 31,
                "question": "48^19 + \u221a169 + 538 - 907 + (73) + (9) + (-22) x (-47)",
                "answer": 87817993537467267453437463232512
            },
            {
                "id": 32,
                "question": "4032 : 64 + 380 - 654",
                "answer": -211
            },
            {
                "id": 33,
                "question": "59 + 350 + 41 x 55 + 6237 : 81",
                "answer": 2741
            },
            {
                "id": 34,
                "question": "6144 : 96 + 27^18",
                "answer": 58149737003040063952519168
            },
            {
                "id": 35,
                "question": "774 - 941 + (-7) : (71) : (-51) - (-15) + 10^9",
                "answer": 999999848
            },
            {
                "id": 36,
                "question": "\u221a1681 + (-19) - (-42) : (-43) + 48 x 12 + 10/ 1 + 2/ 1",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 37,
                "question": "4374 : 81 + 3/ 8 - 9/ 6 x 7/ 4 x 1/ 9 + 62 x 51",
                "answer": 3216
            },
            {
                "id": 38,
                "question": "803 - 13 + 33^18 + 530 : 53 + 465 + 796",
                "answer": 2154025884392726735362195456
            },
            {
                "id": 39,
                "question": "29 x 53 + 7482 : 86 + 423 - 656 + 313 + 152",
                "answer": 1856
            },
            {
                "id": 40,
                "question": "2838 : 33 + 797 + 864",
                "answer": 1747
            },
            {
                "id": 41,
                "question": "2/ 7 x 9/ 10 + 6/ 1 : 5/ 4 + \u221a324",
                "answer": 19
            },
            {
                "id": 42,
                "question": "148 - 374 + 702 + 382",
                "answer": 858
            },
            {
                "id": 43,
                "question": "841 - 610 + 351 + 56 + 54 x 27 + 2496 : 78",
                "answer": 2128
            },
            {
                "id": 44,
                "question": "\u221a81 + 743 - 251 + 38^13 + 510 + 322",
                "answer": 18560658408
            },
            {
                "id": 45,
                "question": "1771 : 77 + \u221a81 + 92 + 163 + 493 - 253",
                "answer": 47
            },
            {
                "id": 46,
                "question": "\u221a900 + 176 : 22",
                "answer": 30
            },
            {
                "id": 47,
                "question": "7040 : 80 + \u221a2500 + 38^13",
                "answer": 18560658496
            },
            {
                "id": 48,
                "question": "\u221a49 + 52 x 55 + 253 + 245 + 2856 : 56",
                "answer": 59
            },
            {
                "id": 49,
                "question": "(-59) - (56) x (-56) + 539 - 458 + 4185 : 93",
                "answer": 3203
            },
            {
                "id": 50,
                "question": "6/ 8 - 4/ 7 x 9/ 1 + \u221a1764",
                "answer": 38
            },
            {
                "id": 51,
                "question": "95 x 10 + \u221a196 + 1^13",
                "answer": 964
            },
            {
                "id": 52,
                "question": "145 - 366 + 611 + 460",
                "answer": 850
            },
            {
                "id": 53,
                "question": "(84) + (-3) + 91 x 50 + 7/ 3 : 9/ 10",
                "answer": 4631
            },
            {
                "id": 54,
                "question": "734 + 602 + 1^5",
                "answer": 1337
            },
            {
                "id": 55,
                "question": "9/ 9 + 7/ 2 x 8/ 8 + \u221a2401 + 965 + 471",
                "answer": 66
            },
            {
                "id": 56,
                "question": "154 : 7 + 2^15 + 10/ 8 : 9/ 8 - 7/ 2 x 7/ 1",
                "answer": 32766
            },
            {
                "id": 57,
                "question": "22 x 46 + \u221a676 + 510 - 766 + 43^11",
                "answer": 963999840
            },
            {
                "id": 58,
                "question": "36^5 + (4) + (-83) + 7/ 2 + 7/ 1 x 8/ 6",
                "answer": 60466110
            },
            {
                "id": 59,
                "question": "6/ 7 + 2/ 6 + (93) + (-53) : (-23) + (-94) + 48^12",
                "answer": 149587343098087735296
            },
            {
                "id": 60,
                "question": "48^18 + 5/ 1 + 2/ 5 : 2/ 3 + \u221a625",
                "answer": 1829541532030568071946613817344
            },
            {
                "id": 61,
                "question": "(20) + (-27) + (7) + (-15) + 290 + 697 + 999 - 961",
                "answer": 1010
            },
            {
                "id": 62,
                "question": "595 - 296 + 4692 : 51",
                "answer": 391
            },
            {
                "id": 63,
                "question": "5/ 5 - 10/ 5 x 1/ 3 + 7/ 1 + 1260 : 18",
                "answer": 77
            },
            {
                "id": 64,
                "question": "\u221a1296 + 30 x 39",
                "answer": 50
            },
            {
                "id": 65,
                "question": "(-85) + (66) + 657 + 543",
                "answer": 1181
            },
            {
                "id": 66,
                "question": "1696 : 53 + 783 + 163 + 18^7 + \u221a1764",
                "answer": 612221052
            },
            {
                "id": 67,
                "question": "792 - 188 + \u221a225 + 57 x 63 + 7/ 3 - 6/ 9 + 3/ 1",
                "answer": 666
            },
            {
                "id": 68,
                "question": "784 - 889 + 1/ 3 x 9/ 6",
                "answer": -104
            },
            {
                "id": 69,
                "question": "644 - 63 + 143 + 1 + 14^17",
                "answer": 30491346729331196629
            },
            {
                "id": 70,
                "question": "\u221a169 + 28^16",
                "answer": 377801998336
            },
            {
                "id": 71,
                "question": "441 : 21 + 669 + 622",
                "answer": 1312
            },
            {
                "id": 72,
                "question": "983 - 614 + 10/ 5 - 2/ 3 - 5/ 7 x 1/ 9 + 18^16 + (38) - (39) + (86)",
                "answer": 121439531096594251776
            },
            {
                "id": 73,
                "question": "\u221a2401 + 308 + 678",
                "answer": 58
            },
            {
                "id": 74,
                "question": "4/ 7 - 10/ 3 + 10/ 2 + (18) : (23) - (53) + 902 + 709",
                "answer": 1561
            },
            {
                "id": 75,
                "question": "848 - 651 + \u221a361",
                "answer": 216
            },
            {
                "id": 76,
                "question": "953 + 268 + 28 : 2",
                "answer": 1235
            },
            {
                "id": 77,
                "question": "\u221a2500 + 739 - 344 + 19^7 + 69 x 61",
                "answer": 29898
            },
            {
                "id": 78,
                "question": "3600 : 75 + 68 x 29 + 49^20",
                "answer": 6366805760909028434057105254645760
            },
            {
                "id": 79,
                "question": "432 : 8 + 7/ 8 - 9/ 8 + 10/ 8 x 2/ 6",
                "answer": 54
            },
            {
                "id": 80,
                "question": "6^4 + 750 : 30",
                "answer": 1321
            },
            {
                "id": 81,
                "question": "541 + 371 + 3/ 9 + 2/ 1 : 4/ 3 + 2088 : 36",
                "answer": 970
            },
            {
                "id": 82,
                "question": "503 + 784 + 17^12 + 64 x 71 + 9/ 10 x 4/ 6",
                "answer": 582622237235593
            },
            {
                "id": 83,
                "question": "2/ 9 + 1/ 1 x 8/ 7 + 657 + 727",
                "answer": 1385
            },
            {
                "id": 84,
                "question": "205 - 307 + 8 x 40 + 55 + 447 + \u221a1024",
                "answer": 752
            },
            {
                "id": 85,
                "question": "814 : 22 + 2/ 9 - 8/ 2 x 9/ 10 + 946 - 880 + 776 + 590",
                "answer": 1466
            },
            {
                "id": 86,
                "question": "\u221a1369 + 2430 : 27 + 700 + 687 + 39^9",
                "answer": 14447434
            },
            {
                "id": 87,
                "question": "5/ 4 : 3/ 2 x 3/ 1 + \u221a784 + 97 x 79",
                "answer": 93
            },
            {
                "id": 88,
                "question": "995 + 652 + (82) + (14)",
                "answer": 1743
            },
            {
                "id": 89,
                "question": "97 x 23 + \u221a1764 + (44) x (76) + 10/ 2 x 4/ 9",
                "answer": 2302
            },
            {
                "id": 90,
                "question": "657 : 9 + 27 x 66 + (-44) + (14) + (36) - (-96) + 4/ 3 x 4/ 4",
                "answer": 1958
            },
            {
                "id": 91,
                "question": "\u221a289 + 6/ 7 + 2/ 5 + 5/ 1 + 723 - 41 + 74 x 49",
                "answer": 68
            },
            {
                "id": 92,
                "question": "6862 : 73 + 299 + 51 + 91 x 45",
                "answer": 4539
            },
            {
                "id": 93,
                "question": "\u221a784 + (46) - (100)",
                "answer": 27
            },
            {
                "id": 94,
                "question": "2640 : 66 + 919 - 975 + 35^7",
                "answer": 64339296859
            },
            {
                "id": 95,
                "question": "19^2 + 1350 : 45 + 588 + 893 + (-67) - (16) - (72) - (13)",
                "answer": 1704
            },
            {
                "id": 96,
                "question": "40 x 74 + 6/ 5 + 8/ 4 : 7/ 7 : 5/ 1 + 2418 : 26",
                "answer": 3054
            },
            {
                "id": 97,
                "question": "25^19 + \u221a1225 + (-86) - (-90) - (-89) x (39)",
                "answer": 363797880709171286976233472
            },
            {
                "id": 98,
                "question": "435 : 29 + (44) : (92)",
                "answer": 15
            },
            {
                "id": 99,
                "question": "836 - 555 + \u221a64 + 68 x 51",
                "answer": 340
            },
            {
                "id": 100,
                "question": "295 + 727 + 85 - 407",
                "answer": 700
            },
            {
                "id": 101,
                "question": "\u221a441 + 435 - 330 + 2277 : 99 + 17 x 14",
                "answer": 28
            },
            {
                "id": 102,
                "question": "(81) - (32) - (-96) x (15) + 21^12",
                "answer": 7355827511388130
            },
            {
                "id": 103,
                "question": "(-17) - (69) x (-7) : (-93) + 124 + 977 + 9/ 9 : 1/ 4 + 19^13",
                "answer": 42052983462258136
            },
            {
                "id": 104,
                "question": "42 x 20 + 555 + 665 + 1292 : 38 + (89) x (-24) + (72) x (-45)",
                "answer": -3282
            },
            {
                "id": 105,
                "question": "6006 : 77 + (96) x (-31) + \u221a1849 + 50 x 41",
                "answer": -2836
            },
            {
                "id": 106,
                "question": "2550 : 85 + \u221a676",
                "answer": 56
            },
            {
                "id": 107,
                "question": "128 - 362 + 3^1",
                "answer": -231
            },
            {
                "id": 108,
                "question": "6800 : 100 + (-63) - (25) : (94) + (23)",
                "answer": 28
            },
            {
                "id": 109,
                "question": "\u221a1936 + 20^17",
                "answer": 114486680448
            },
            {
                "id": 110,
                "question": "236 : 59 + (65) x (-40) : (-10) : (-97) + 936 - 279 + 29 + 932",
                "answer": 1619
            },
            {
                "id": 111,
                "question": "1080 : 36 + 684 + 105",
                "answer": 819
            },
            {
                "id": 112,
                "question": "5^6 + 281 - 752",
                "answer": 15154
            },
            {
                "id": 113,
                "question": "\u221a484 + (-93) : (3) - (74) : (42)",
                "answer": 21
            },
            {
                "id": 114,
                "question": "412 + 666 + 36^1 + 2888 : 76 + 30 x 14",
                "answer": 1572
            },
            {
                "id": 115,
                "question": "84 x 26 + 267 - 229 + (1) x (100) - (8) x (-22)",
                "answer": 2498
            },
            {
                "id": 116,
                "question": "1566 : 87 + 63 x 46 + (-30) - (97) + (17) + (-88)",
                "answer": 2718
            },
            {
                "id": 117,
                "question": "895 + 662 + 67 x 4 + 343 - 843",
                "answer": 1325
            },
            {
                "id": 118,
                "question": "(-10) + (63) + (-99) x (-78) + 58 x 79 + 518 - 168",
                "answer": 12707
            },
            {
                "id": 119,
                "question": "45^3 + 2156 : 98",
                "answer": 91147
            },
            {
                "id": 120,
                "question": "30 x 44 + 592 + 713",
                "answer": 2625
            },
            {
                "id": 121,
                "question": "(-19) : (-30) : (60) + 870 + 518 + 494 - 817 + \u221a256",
                "answer": 1081
            },
            {
                "id": 122,
                "question": "4779 : 59 + 17^5 + (-34) + (-38) + \u221a1156",
                "answer": 1419900
            },
            {
                "id": 123,
                "question": "1008 : 72 + 18^1 + 623 - 285",
                "answer": 370
            },
            {
                "id": 124,
                "question": "50 x 1 + \u221a49 + 5/ 2 - 10/ 7",
                "answer": 57
            },
            {
                "id": 125,
                "question": "1566 : 54 + 14^17 + (84) x (-48) : (58) + \u221a1936",
                "answer": 30491346729331195904
            },
            {
                "id": 126,
                "question": "4104 : 57 + (6) x (-66) - (9) x (75) + 1/ 5 : 6/ 6",
                "answer": -999
            },
            {
                "id": 127,
                "question": "687 - 835 + 354 + 136 + (26) + (10)",
                "answer": 378
            },
            {
                "id": 128,
                "question": "5607 : 63 + 5/ 4 + 5/ 7 x 7/ 2 : 8/ 5 + (-61) : (-65) x (42)",
                "answer": 130
            },
            {
                "id": 129,
                "question": "811 + 473 + 988 : 19 + 624 - 551",
                "answer": 1409
            },
            {
                "id": 130,
                "question": "(36) + (-29) + (-16) x (88) + 5/ 1 : 5/ 8 + 2/ 10 + 3/ 1 + 341 + 966 + \u221a256",
                "answer": -75
            },
            {
                "id": 131,
                "question": "(53) x (-9) + 845 + 145 + 8/ 8 x 7/ 10 - 5/ 10",
                "answer": 513
            },
            {
                "id": 132,
                "question": "5/ 7 + 1/ 10 - 2/ 3 + 43^15 + \u221a529",
                "answer": 3177070365797955464593408
            },
            {
                "id": 133,
                "question": "87 x 29 + (-18) + (-85) : (58) + 45^4",
                "answer": 4103129
            },
            {
                "id": 134,
                "question": "\u221a484 + (1) - (48) + 699 + 693 + 7/ 9 : 6/ 10",
                "answer": 43
            },
            {
                "id": 135,
                "question": "3/ 1 - 6/ 6 + (-51) : (85) x (-20) + (9) + 398 + 693 + 29 x 46",
                "answer": 2448
            },
            {
                "id": 136,
                "question": "660 - 504 + 1512 : 18 + 85 x 95 + 371 + 970",
                "answer": 9656
            },
            {
                "id": 137,
                "question": "6/ 6 - 4/ 4 + \u221a529",
                "answer": 23
            },
            {
                "id": 138,
                "question": "27^11 + \u221a1849 + 325 - 855",
                "answer": 5559060566555559
            },
            {
                "id": 139,
                "question": "(55) x (-77) + 940 + 477 + 691 - 62",
                "answer": -2189
            },
            {
                "id": 140,
                "question": "499 + 348 + 10^20 + (58) : (68) + (-94)",
                "answer": 100000000000000000000
            },
            {
                "id": 141,
                "question": "\u221a2401 + (42) : (-40) x (50) + 6/ 7 + 6/ 2 x 4/ 5 x 4/ 5",
                "answer": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 142,
                "question": "\u221a144 + 561 - 696 + (-24) : (89) + (25)",
                "answer": 6
            },
            {
                "id": 143,
                "question": "875 + 856 + (60) + (25) - (88) + 3^8 + 644 : 28",
                "answer": 8312
            },
            {
                "id": 144,
                "question": "4/ 2 x 6/ 6 + 391 - 733 + \u221a784 + (-70) x (8) - (41)",
                "answer": -326
            },
            {
                "id": 145,
                "question": "\u221a1089 + 2494 : 86",
                "answer": 33
            },
            {
                "id": 146,
                "question": "(-27) : (56) - (-94) : (64) + 820 + 116",
                "answer": 937
            },
            {
                "id": 147,
                "question": "604 - 388 + 192 + 465 + 2/ 6 + 10/ 7 - 3/ 9 + 3404 : 74",
                "answer": 920
            },
            {
                "id": 148,
                "question": "\u221a25 + 27 x 90 + 80 + 664 + 108 - 962",
                "answer": 48
            },
            {
                "id": 149,
                "question": "537 - 344 + 17^16 + 5/ 10 - 9/ 5",
                "answer": 48661191875666870272
            },
            {
                "id": 150,
                "question": "1/ 1 : 4/ 7 - 9/ 4 + 62 x 11 + \u221a1 + 529 + 624",
                "answer": 714
            }
        ]
    }
}